What if you had a universal remote...that controlled your universe?
Click is a comedy, drama, fantasy film directed by Frank Coraci.
A married workaholic, Michael Newman doesn't have time for his wife and children, not if
he's to impress his ungrateful boss and earn a well-deserved promotion.
So when he meets Morty, a loopy sales clerk, he gets the answer to his prayers: a magical remote that
allows him to bypass life's little distractions with increasingly hysterical results.
Michael Newman, played by Adam Sandler.
Donna Newman, played by Kate Beckinsale.
Morty, played by Christopher Walken.
Ammer, played by David Hasselhoff.
Ted, played by Henry Winkler.
Trudy, played by Julie Kavner.
Click is a 2006 American fantasy comedy-drama film directed by Frank Coraci, written by Steve
Koren and Mark O'Keefe, both of whom produced with Jack Giarraputo, Neal H.
Moritz, and Adam Sandler, who also starred in the lead role.
The film co-stars Kate Beckinsale, Christopher Walken, Henry
Winkler, David Hasselhoff, Julie Kavner, and Sean Astin.
Sandler plays Michael Newman, a workaholic family man and architect who acquires
a magical universal remote that enables him to control reality.
The film is inspired by "The Magic Thread", a folk tale included in
The Book of Virtues: A Treasury of Great Moral Stories.
Filming began in late 2005 and was finished by early 2006.
Sony Pictures Releasing, under Columbia Pictures, released Click in the
United States on June 23, 2006, and received mixed reviews.
It was made on a budget of $85 million and grossed $268.7 million.
It was nominated for Best Makeup at the 79th Academy
Awards (it lost the award to Pan's Labyrinth).
This makes Click the only Sandler-produced film to
be nominated for an Academy Award.
The film explores themes of dying and death, regret,
workaholic, heart attack, architect.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.